## Personal Info

Date of birth: 9/1/1987

Address: Bat-Yam

#### Contact

0502345096 (Mobile) shimonfiller@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shimon-filler-514b76163 (LinkedIn)

## Education

The Open University of Israel Bachelor's degree, Computer Science And Education (2015-2021).

## Top Skills

React

Redux-Toolkit

**TypeScript** 

Flex-Box

CSS-Grid

Cypress

## **Certifications**

#### <u>Udemy:</u>

- React The Ultimate React Course 2022.
- Cypress End-to-End Testing.
- CSS The Complete Guide.
- Angular Ngrx (with ngrx DATA).
- Angular Reactive Angular Course (with Rxjs).
- Angular The Complete Guide (2021 Edition).

# Shimon Filler

## **Frontend Developer**

\*Portfolio website:

https://my-portfolio-87888.web.app/



# **Summary**

5 years of experience in web development. For the last 2 years in the industry, I have worked as a React developer for a start-up company in the field of fintech. I'm a dedicated worker, and I am always looking for more practical knowledge in my profession to perfect my skills.

## **Experience**

#### **Sunbit**

React Developer

December 2021 - October 2023

The role involved intensive teamwork using the Agile methodology. Leading technologies and skills: Redux-Toolkit, Typescript, Detox, Cypress, Styled-Components, storybook.

## **Self-employed**

Frontend Developer

January 2019 - October 2021

As I studied to finish my degree, I developed my FE skills by learning angular At Udemy.

I developed a chat website for learning purposes and used Firebase as the Backend and hosting.

Link: https://mychatapp4-1f82e.web.app/chat.

Repo: https://github.com/sfiller23/myChatApp.

Leading technologies: Firebase, Ngrx, Rxjs. Bootstap5.

Additionally, I built a website for a metal band using Django and a website for a personal fitness trainer using WordPress.

## **Indigo Immigration services**

Full Stack Developer

February 2016 - April 2017

- Maintained company sites using jQuery and Vanilla JS to ensure smooth functionality.
- Managed a PHP-built CRM site for efficient customer relationship management.
- Implemented UI/UX enhancements to boost user experience and drive increased site traffic.